Today I would like to talk to you about traveling with your pet rat.
Pet rats love to go places with you, they are very intelligent, and they love to travel and they love to be with their friends.
It is fun to take your pet rat to your friend's house or maybe you may be going to the veterinarian or maybe you may be going to a rat show.
I have here four different travel cases for your rat.
This one is an awesome one, I love this one, the top of it zips open.
It has a little window in it so your rat can get air.
So you put your rat in the travel carrier and you can zip it up.
And there is no way for your rat to get out unless he chews his way out.
The great thing about this one is that it is a back pack.
You can put it on your back or your front, as you carry your rat with you and you can put multiple rats in here, unless he decides to chew out.
This is a wonderful carrier.
These carriers should not be left with your rat alone anywhere, because they can chew the cloth and get out of the rat carrier and then he would be gone.
You should not leave your rat unattended in a car or anywhere.
The second one I am going to show you is this carrier, this is my favorite one.
This has a little door, so put your rat in the little door, and zip it up.
And it has lots of different windows, it has plastic windows, and doors that also opens this way.
It has two handles, this is like the Gucci bag to rat carriers.
You can also carry multiple rats in this carrier.
The third one I am going to show you is a cat carrier, you can buy this to put your cat or chihuahua dog in.
This one is a little fancier, and it is not as secure as the other carriers are, since the rat can get out of this one, but it is awfully pretty.
You put your rat inside and zip it up.
But as you can see, you rat can sneak out in the front.
It is not as secure as the other carriers, but as long as you are not leaving your rat unattended, they cannot get out and disappear on you.